hey everybody out there review on this
Festool wrote X 150 probably the best
sander I won't well is the best sander I
own if you have a lot of Dewalt sanders
but they definitely do not cut it when
it comes to cleaner off wood like this
so this is basically a chunk of maple
that's been stripped and I'm just gonna
be cutting through the stain we've got
it in Rotax direct drive that's some 80
grit iridium paper now hooked up to dust
collection and I'm just gonna show you
how fast you can strip a table off here
especially if you're into mass
production you definitely faster you can
sand stuff the more money you'll make
[Music]
there you could go you could see how
fast that cuts right through bring the
camera over here some have a better luck
and you can see that's got its trip rate
down nice using some meridiem sandpaper
main reason for this sander is we
started getting into mass production
like we have going on here and you got
over 50 tables to do last thing you want
to be do is spend in half an hour 45
minutes on a table sanded so these 50
tables I've started these probably half
an hour ago and I think I've got thirty
done so this will be less than an hour
to sand 50 tables and that thing is a
beast and you got to have this little
bad boy here to suck up that dust there
you go